<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="English_Hymn1">
        <item>1. The Lord He is very gra-cious In Mercy He’s Plenteous And he doth great compression show; But unto wrath doth slow. </item>
        <item>2. Good unto all Man is the Lord’ Who calls in truth on him, O’er all his work his Mercy is, Of great lib’rality.</item>
        <item>3. The works all Praise  to thee afford; For all that thou hast done.Thy saints, O Lord thy name shall blessAnd show great Joy in Thee.</item>
        <item>4. The glory of thy kingdom show Forever bless his name Shall they and of thy power tell The greatness of thy might.</item>
        <item>5. ‘That so men’s sons his deeds may know’ Great and wonderful thing ‘His kingdom’s glories that excel’ Beyond Man’s great knowledge.</item>
        <item>6. Thy kingdom hath none end at all; I will thee bless and sing. ‘it doth through ages all remain; And ever, so shall be. </item>
        <item>7. The Lord upholdeth all that fall, His eyes attend to them, The cast down raiseth up again, They that wait upon Him.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="English_Hymn2">
        <item>1. O come and let us sing Unto the Lord, our God O let us our Rock and Saviour sing Who saves us all in love.</item>
        <item>2. Let us before Him come With thanksgiving and praise And show ourselves with songs of joy And sing unto His name.</item>
        <item>3. The Lord is a great God; A great King over all His kingdom forever shall be Without an end at all.</item>
        <item>4. Within His are hands are all The corners of the earth; And all the lofty hills on earth Are all within His hand.</item>
        <item>5. The sea He also made And it belongs to him And with His hand this earth He made And thus be glorified.</item>
        <item>6. O come, let us worship And do bow down in pray’r And kneel before the Lord and King Our maker and our friend.</item>
        <item>7. For He’s the Lord our God; And we shall be His flock The flock He pastures, cares and loves And sherphered by Himself.</item>
        <item>8. O hear the Lord His voice O hear Him speaking know And harden not your heart, for now The patient time is gone.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="English_Hymn3">
        <item>1. All people that on earth do dwell, Sing to the Lord with cheerful voice, Him serve with mirth, His praise forth tell;Come ye before Him and rejoice. </item>
        <item>2. The Lord ye know, is God in deed; Without our aid He did us make; We are His folk, He doth us feed; And for His sheep He doth us take.</item>
        <item>3. O enter then His gates with praise, Approach with joy His courts unto. Praise, laud, and bless His name always For it is seemly so to do. </item>
        <item>4. For why!  The Lord our God is good His mercy is for ever sure; His truth at all times firmly stood,And shall from ages to ages endure.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
